https://medimobile.com/privacy-policy/

About MediMobile Charge Capture Solution Privacy Policy
Skip to content
HomeAbout UsFAQsReviewsContact UsCurrent User SupportSolutionsCharge CaptureMediMoveMedical BillingEventsNewsroomGet StartedLog InCurrent User SupportHomeAbout UsFAQsReviewsContact UsCurrent User SupportSolutionsCharge CaptureMediMoveMedical BillingEventsNewsroomGet StartedLog InCurrent User SupportHomeAbout UsFAQsReviewsContact UsCurrent User SupportSolutionsCharge CaptureMediMoveMedical BillingEventsNewsroomGet StartedLog InCurrent User Support
Privacy Policymedimobile2019-04-24T15:02:43-05:00
Privacy Policy
JPG Technologies, Inc. (JPG) respects your privacy. Across our business, we will only collect, store and use your personal information for defined purposes. We use your information to support and enhance our relationship with you, for example, to process your purchase, provide service and support, and share product, service and company news and offerings with you. We do not sell your personal information. We only share your personal data outside the JPG family of companies with your consent, as required by law or to protect JPG, its customers, or the public, or with companies that help JPG fulfill its obligations with you, and then only with partners who share JPG’s commitment to protecting your privacy and data. At any time you may contact JPG with any privacy questions or concerns you may have. You also may ask at any time to see the personal data you have given us and request correction or deletion. We strive to protect the security of your personal data by use of appropriate measures and processes.
Privacy and Data Security
At JPG, your right to privacy and data security is a primary concern. That’s why, when you visit safetextmd.com or medimobile.com, we help you maintain control over your personal data on the Internet. Below are the guidelines we use for protecting the information you provide us during a visit to our Internet site or when you use our online support offerings such as www.safetextmd.com, www.medimobile.com or support applications loaded on your computer or handheld device. Other JPG and JPG co-branded sites may operate under their own privacy and security policies.
JPG’s Privacy statement discloses the privacy guidelines for the entire domestic JPG Web site. The guidelines at this site are applicable only to this domestic Web site.
JPG only asks for specific types of personal information
In a few areas on our Web site and online customer support tools, we ask you to provide information that will enable us to enhance your site visit, to assist you with purchase and technical support issues or to follow up with you after your visit. It is completely optional for you to participate.
For example, we request information from you when you:
1. Register on safetextmd.com or medimobile.com
2. Place an order
3. Provide feedback in an online survey
4. Participate in a sweepstakes or other promotional offer
5. Subscribe to a newsletter or a mailing list
6. Fill out a support request
Information we may request includes your name, e-mail address, phone number, address, type of business, credit card details, customer preference information, and account number, as well as other similar personal information. If we ever ask for significantly different information we will inform you.
JPG only uses your personal information for specific purposes.
The information you provide will be kept confidential and used to support your customer relationship with JPG. Among other things, we want to help you quickly find information on safetextmd.com or medimobile.com and alert you to product upgrades, special offers, updated information and other new products and services from JPG. Agents or contractors of JPG who have access to your personal information and prospect information are required to keep the information confidential and not use it for any other purpose than to carry out the services they are performing for JPG. JPG may enhance or merge your information collected at its site with data from third parties for purposes of marketing products or services to you.
In addition, JPG may be required to disclose personal information in connection with law enforcement, fraud prevention, regulation, and other legal action or if JPG reasonably believes it is necessary to do so to protect JPG, its customers, or the public.
You can opt-out of JPG’s marketing list at any time
Periodically, we may send you information about our various products and services, or other products and services we feel may be of interest to you. Only JPG (or agents working on behalf of JPG and under confidentiality agreements) will send you these direct mailings. If you do not want to be included on JPG’s marketing list, simply tell us when you give us your personal information. Or, at any time you can easily opt-out of JPG’s marketing list.
JPG will not disclose your personal information to any outside organization for its use in marketing without your consent
Information regarding you (such as name, address and phone number) or your order and the products you purchase will not be given or sold to any outside organization for its use in marketing or solicitation without your consent. Your information may be shared with agents or contractors of JPG for the purpose of performing services for JPG.
Internet Commerce
The online store at safetextmd.com or medimobile.com is designed to give you options concerning the privacy of your credit card information, name, address, e-mail and any other information you provide us. JPG is committed to data security with respect to information collected on our site. We offer the industry standard security measures available through your browser called SSL encryption, (please see JPG’s Store Security page for details on these security measures). If at any time you would like to make a purchase, but do not want to provide your credit card information online, you may contact a sales representative over the telephone. Simply call 1-512-275-1810. It has always been a JPG practice to contact customers in the event of a potential problem with your purchase or any normal business communication regarding your purchase.
Customized Experience
We use technology to help us deliver customized visitor experiences. At JPG, we primarily use “cookies” to help us determine which service and support information is appropriate to your machine and to maintain your shopping experience in our online store. Our use of this technology does not mean that we automatically know any information about you. We might be able to ascertain what type of computer you are using, but beyond that, our use of cookies is designed only to provide you with a better experience when using www.safetextmd.com and www.medimobile.com. JPG has no desire or intent to infringe on your privacy while using the JPG.com site.
Third-Party Sites
Please be aware that other web sites that may be accessed through our site may collect personally identifiable information about you. The information practices of those third-party web sites linked to safetextmd.com or medimobile.com are not covered by this privacy statement.
You are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords or any account information. Please be careful and responsible whenever you’re online. If you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return. While we strive to protect your personal information, JPG cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk.
Other Web Sites
JPG’s Web site contains links to other Web sites that are not operated by JPG. JPG is not responsible for the privacy practices of the Web sites that it does not operate. Some parts of the Web site are animated using various downloadable applications, such as Macromedia’s Shockwave/Flash.
Contact JPG
JPG is the sole operator of the JPG, safetextmd and MediMobile Web site. If you would like to contact us for any reason regarding our privacy practices, please write us at the following address:
JPG Technologies, Inc.
Attention: Privacy
1918 Leander Rd.
Georgetown, Texas 78828
Changes to the Policy
Privacy Statement Effective Date: July 17, 2006
Material changes to this policy will be posted on JPG’s Web site for 30 days.
Copyright 2020 JPG Technologies, Inc., All Rights Reserved. CPT® is registered trademark of the American Medical Association.
